http://www.zanotta.it/en-us/privacy-policy

What are you looking for?
Privacy Policy
Dear User/Browser,When browsing our website, depending on the functions used, some of your personal data may be collected and processed; pursuant to and for the purposes of Reg. EU 2016/679 we give you some information relating to the handling of your personal data, not only to satisfy requirements by law, but also for transparency and correctness are founding principles of our company.Please note that your data will be handled in compliance with the aforementioned legislation and regulations and in respect of confidentiality obligations in them under the principles of correctness, lawfulness, transparency and protection of your privacy.The Data Controller of your personal data is Zanotta S.p.A., and is responsible for the legitimate and correct use of your personal data. You may contact them for any information or request using the following details:Data Controller: Zanotta S.p.A.Headquarters: Via Vittorio Veneto 57 – 20834 Nova Milanese (MB), ItalyContact Details:Telephone: +39 0362 4981 - E-mail: zanottaspa@zanotta.itFor some aspects regarding the purposes of processing (as for example Website hosting, management, press agency, e-mail marketing platform, digital agency) we have nominated Data Processors accordingly for your personal data, acting on behalf of Zanotta S.p.A., who are responsible for ensuring the legitimate and correct use of your personal data and can be contacted for any information or request (the specific details of the Processors nominated and their contact details are available on request from the offices of the Data Controller).These parties, where necessary, are suitably qualified with compliance checks relating to compliance with the regulations cited above regarding the Protection of Personal Data.Your personal data are collected and processed for the purposes described below as well as the relevant legal basis:Purpose:Contact the userCollection Methods:Filling in of the contact form for requesting information from the companyData Processed:Name, address or other personally identifiable information, Contact details (telephone number, e-mail, etc.), ProfessionPurpose:Sending of Newsletters and communication relating to events, promotions, etc.Collection Methods:Subscription to newsletter service on filling out the contact form or during registration for the restricted areaData Processed:Name, address or other personally identifiable information, contact details (telephone number, e-mail, etc.), professionPurpose:Registration on the website and access to the restricted areaCollection Methods:Registration for the restricted area via the registration formData Processed:Name, address or other personally identifiable information, contact details (telephone number, e-mail, etc.), professionPurpose:Optimisation of the browsing experience on the websiteCollection Methods:Consent to the use of cookies delivered via banners when opening the website.Data Processed:Cookies requiredPurpose:Statistical analysis relating to browsingCollection Methods:Consent to the use of cookies delivered via banners when opening the website.Data Processed:Anonymised Analytical CookiesPurpose:Customisation of advertising content through the use of profiling cookiesCollection Methods:Consent to the use of cookies delivered via banners when opening the website.Data Processed:First party profiling cookies, third party profiling cookiesLegal basis: Consent givenReg. EU 2016/679 Art. 6 Par.1 Letter a)Your data may be sent to recipients or the categories of recipients detailed below in order to comply with legal obligations or for the purposes relating to the service itself.Categories of recipients:Google AnalyticsThird party cookie managersCompanies or collaborators that supply services on behalf of the data controllerAs well as this information, in order to guarantee the correct and transparent handling of your data, you should be aware that:• Your personal data is handled and stored by the data controller - Zanotta S.p.A. or by data processors on behalf of the controller; the handling and storing of data handled is carried out in paper or electronic format with storage located at the company's headquarters as indicated, or in some cases at the premises of the data processors as named and indicated. At the data controller's premises, your personal data may be handled by persons explicitly authorised to do so by the data controller according to organisational requirements of the controller and in complete compliance with the principles of Regulation EU 2016/679     • All handling is carried out in respect of articles 6 and 32 of Regulation EU 2016/679 and through the adoption of adequate security measures.• The duration of handling, in respect of the principles of law, limitations of the purposes and minimisation of data is determined by a time period no longer than required for the completion of the purposes for which the data was collected and processed, in respect of the legally required time limits.• You have the right to request access to your personal data from the data controller and the correction or deletion of the same or the limiting of the processing on your data, or revoke consent to handling of such data.• If you have given consent for one or more of the specific purposes, you have the right to revoke such consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing undertaken up to the point of consent being revoked.• You have the right to complain to the following Regulatory Authority: Personal Data Protection Authority.• You have the right of portability of your personal data, if compatible with the nature and modes of processing of that data.• The handling is carried out using automated processes that, using some types of cookies as a reference, may be profile interested users.• Some personal data, with reference to Cookies may be transferred to parties outside of the European Union, under the terms of applicable regulations and compliance decisions made by the European Commission.• Your personal data will not be distributed in any form.
